name: 'More Irregular Verbs'
questions:
  -
    question: 'I $ with my manager about my job yesterday.'
    answers:
      - speak
      - spoke
      - spoken
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'My Mom $ dinner last night. It was so good!'
    answers:
      - maked
      - maded
      - made
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'He can''t go to school because he $ his leg last week.'
    answers:
      - broke
      - break
      - broken
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'We just $ from vacation and we don''t want to work!'
    answers:
      - 'come backed'
      - 'comed back'
      - 'came back'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'Bob $ he was hungry, so I made him a sandwich.'
    answers:
      - sayd
      - said
      - sayed
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They $ a new car last month. It''s very beautiful.'
    answers:
      - buyed
      - bought
      - bout
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ a job! Now I''m a doctor.'
    answers:
      - finded
      - founded
      - found
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'We $ your friend Zack in the shopping mall yesterday.'
    answers:
      - meet
      - met
      - meted
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ find my keys yesterday. Did you see them?'
    answers:
      - could
      - 'couldn''t'
      - 'can''t'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'We $ a new ''Walking Dead'' episode two days ago. So scary!'
    answers:
      - saw
      - see
      - seen
    correct: 1
